how it show of hands how many of you
heard the phrase growing up you
can be anything you want to be did you
hear that
yeah what a crock that turned out to be
i wanted to play in the nba
turns out i'm short i'm slow and i can't
jump
not a good resume but it wasn't about it
we're middle school and my best friend
i'll call him alan because that was his
name and uh
they said you can be anything you want
and you're like dude i'm going to be a
model and i'm like dude you're ugly
you can't be whatever you want to be i
actually did an event with the nba a few
years ago met shaquille o'neal you guys
know zach is right and i literally i
walked where i started dying laughing my
buddy said what's so funny i said what
have they told shaq that grown up you be
anything you want to be no we can't what
if shaq's dream in life is to be a
professional horse jockey
[Music]
imagine those horses
and you start learning it through life
like i worked fast food as a teenager
anybody else work fast food yes these
are my people
never give fast food workers a hard time
i don't care what you got what happened
don't give them a hard time i was in
line behind a guy the other day and he's
just like and just reaming the poor
little girl going and said don't pick a
lot of sounds you talk about that don't
just take them because of you
this girl's in tears like i'm sorry i'm
so sorry i'm sorry if she goes back
there and i'm thinking i didn't say it
but i want to go dude you paid five
bucks you got food in a bag be happy
but i didn't because if you've ever
worked for fast food you know this
happened i don't know what was on his
sandwich when it went behind the counter
he's not to want what's on it when it
comes back
and then i see jobs i could not do
they have road construction here in
provo
that was a bit of a rhetorical question
they got guys in the in the
neighborhoods that stand there with that
sign stop
slow
stop
now these guys get paid really well but
i'm just telling you i could not do that
job with my personality after about a
half hour i would start messing with
people
stop stop stop stop
stop
what really cracks me up as these guys
wear hard hats
is that in case the sign falls off or
something that just makes me laugh
then i got to thinking other jobs i
could not do i flew out here from
atlanta georgia and i flew to salt lake
and it was awesome but i love flight
attendants i love them i could not do
that job
one flight of having to stand up at that
door at the end of every flight okay
bye-bye okay bye okay bye-bye okay
the part i really couldn't do was the
part they were acquired by law
to do at the beginning of every flight
to fasten your seat belt
put this end into this end
to release pull up on me
i'm telling you i would snap
direct two attention to candy's gonna
show you how to fasten your seatbelt
okay
okay okay
you know what if we're in a crash and
you can't figure this out
you deserve to die
and if we lose cabin pressure and
there's a bright yellow oxygen mask
swinging in front of your face
and you can't figure out breathe
maybe your dna does not need to be
passed on
the
end of the flight
at the end of the flight ladies and
gentlemen it's our final approach please
put your tray tables and seat backs to
the full and upright position
why
really why this okay
safe unsaved
unsafe
death life death life
[Applause]
i've got a i've got a cousin who's a
flight attendant i said what is up with
the tray tables and she said i'm not
making this up she said well in case of
an emergency evacuation we don't want
anybody to get trapped
i would pay to see that
everybody evacuate immediately okay
my tree table
i couldn't do that job
oh i saw one job one job i've done this
for over three decades so one job in
three decades that if i didn't do this i
would want to do i was in phoenix
arizona but he might have picked me up
in a convertible i'm like dude this is
awesome
i said what are you doing it rains he
goes only rains twice a year
that night i do the show i go back to
the hotel i turn on the tv in phoenix
arizona where it rains twice a year they
actually have
a weather man
i would love that job
let's go to canada weather center okay
if you notice on the map here you'll
notice that we live in a desert
we're going to live in here and say it's
going to be hot tomorrow
let's take a look at the five-month
forecast
heart back here
[Music]
you